WESLEY W JENSEN

SUMMARY

I am a Front-End Developer whose proficiency is in JavaScript, Node.js and React.js. I have a year of experience with Front-End Development, thanks to Thinkful and Codecademy. As a side note, I am also very interested in Arduino/Raspberry.

SKILLS

Technical skills: JavaScript, HTML, CSS, Node.js, React.js and Express, PostgreSQL. Native-level English. Intermediate-level Spanish. Beginner-level Japanese.

Relevant Side skills: PostgreSQL, Knex.js, RESTful APIs

Tools: VSCode, Bootstrap, MS Excel, Google Suite, Unity3D, Postman, elephantSQL, AWS, DBeaver, GitHub, Heroku, Vercel

PROJECTS

ThinkfulBnB - HTML + CSS Website Project

ThinkfulBnB was a task that provided a website full of information, but lacked functional structure. I completed the website by enacting requested fonts, colors and perfected the responsive format of the website.

Local Library - <u>Java and HTML focused Project</u>

Local Library is a project that consists of many JS files that have been compiled to create a site that organizes books in a library. I've elected to use Qualified to finish this project.

ILoveMovies - PostgreSQL + Node and Express

Upon being provided the ERD for a backend app, I fulfilled the map and efficiently created a functional movies database. When connected to a frontend, this app can search movies by theater or showing status.

EXPERIENCE

Stillfire Brewing, Suwanee — Service and Tech

Aug 2019 - July 2020

- Serviced customers and routinely cleaned.
- Exchanged all barrels and maintained serving tanks.
- Worked security detail and led security and identification teams of up to 5 people.
- Actively listened to customers.
- Constantly maintained barrel rooms and proactively cleaned chairs + tables.

Dunkin' Donuts, Johns Creek - Cashier and Baker

May 2017 - March 2018

- Maintained transactions as a Cashier.
- Helped cater a friendly environment as a greeter.
- Baked and prepared all the foodstuffs.
- Nightly ensured presentation of all foodstuffs, closed store and maintained equipment.
- Fulfilled two weekly catering orders.

EDUCATION

Thinkful, Online - Certification

April 2021 - February 2022, Remote